http://www.stressbusting.co.uk/privacy/

Aromatherapy
Autogenic (AT)
Ayurvedic Medicine
Biofeedback
Breathing
Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT)
Hypnotherapy
Kinesiology (Applied)
Laughter therapy
Massage
Meditation
Mindfulness (MBSR)
Music Therapy
Neuro-linguistic programming (NLP)
Search
You are here:
Stressbusting > Privacy
INTRODUCTION
Welcome to www.stressbusting.co.uk or www.stressbusting.com (“Site”), which is owned and operated by Zonkly Limited (‘Zonkly Limited’, ‘we’, ‘our’ or ’us’ as applicable). For further detailed information about this Site and your use of its features, please see our Terms and Conditions.
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of users of the Site, whilst ensuring that you receive a high quality service. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide.
Please refer to our Cookie Policy if you would like detailed information on the types of cookies we use on the Site, the purposes for which we use each cookie, how you can withdraw your consent to the use of certain cookies and the consequences of doing so.
Please note that by visiting and using the Site you are agreeing to the use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.
If you have any queries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at admin@stressbusting.co.uk.
THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
If you place an order for a physical product, we will also collect further information, including your telephone number and your postal address.
If you post any text, images, videos or other user generated content, we collect any personal information contained in that content that content e.g. personal information that included in a photo that you upload of yourself.
If you sign up to our newsletter / e-alert service, we collect personal information such as your name and email address and country of residence.
We use this information:
If you have chosen to receive our newsletter, to send you the latest news and updates from our Site.
If you link your social media network account to the Site, to facilitate sharing between the Site and that network.
HOW ELSE MAY WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may use your personal information to investigate a complaint made by another user or any potential breach of the Site’s Terms and Conditions and to prevent and detect criminal activity, fraud and misuse of, or damage to, the Site or the services made available through it and to take appropriate legal action against those responsible.
INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE
We do not sell or rent your personal information. We may, however, give information about you to the following, for the express purposes set out below.
If you register with the Site:
to our employees and agents (who may be operating outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”)) for them to administer the services provided to you through the Site.
If you place an order:
to our employees and agents for them to provide support services in connection with the Site, for example delivery services;
and if you pay by credit card, to the appropriate payment provider in order for it to authorise and approve your card and for it to process the card transaction.
Transfer of business
if ownership or operational control of all or part of the Site were transferred, whether as part of the sale of the Site or of Zonkly Limited or otherwise, we may disclose your personal information to the transferee.
If that happens, we would require them to use your information in a way that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Legal Requests
We may need to disclose personal information to protect our and our licensors’ rights and property or to comply with any applicable law or valid legal process.
If we do give your information to any third parties in the circumstances set out above, we always require they adhere to the same security procedures that we follow ourselves.
TRANSFER OF INFORMATION OUTSIDE EEA
Your information may be transferred to, stored at, or processed at a destination outside the EEA. It may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services.
By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
COOKIES AND AGGREGATED INFORMATION
Cookies and log files
While on the Site, certain information is automatically logged about how you are using the Site. This information may include the URL of the website which linked you to this Site, your IP address and the pages you visit while on the website. The IP address indicates the location of your computer on the internet. IP addresses are not used to track your session and are not linked to anything personally identifiable.
Like many websites we may use a feature called a cookie. Please refer to our Cookie Policy if you would like detailed information on the types of cookies we use on the Site, the purposes for which we use each cookie, how you can withdraw your consent to the use of certain cookies and the consequences of doing so.
Aggregated information
We may share non-personal aggregated statistics data about visitors to this Site and sales and traffic patterns with third parties. Just to be clear, this information does not identify users in any personal capacity; it just gives generalised information about the users of our Site.
LINKS
The Site contains links to third party websites that are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We strongly recommend that you read the privacy policy of any such websites that you visit.
HOW DO WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
As required by UK Data Protection law, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us, to prevent unauthorised access. In particular, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to encode your personal information. SSL encrypts your contact details and your password as it travels through the Internet. Encryption creates billions of code combinations to protect each transaction made on the Site, so your details cannot be viewed by anyone else using the internet.
Despite using this technology, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you disclose to us. You accept the inherent risks of providing information and dealing on-line and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful default.
You should be aware that the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory authorities of countries outside the EEA, in addition to those within the EEA, may be able to obtain access to or disclosure of your personal information through the laws of their respective countries.
If you have any concerns about security, please email us at admin@stressbusting.co.uk
UNSUBSCRIBING FROM MARKETING EMAILS
If you have consented to receiving marketing emails, you can withdraw this consent by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in any marketing communication that we [or our commercial partners] send to you.
ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Under the Data Protection Act you have the right to see the personal information that we hold about you, whether collected through your use of this Site or through any communications that you have had with us. You will need to provide us with a written request and pay a small fee. If you have any queries about your right or wish to make such a request please contact us by e-mail at admin@stressbusting.co.uk or by post addressed to the Data Protection Officer, Zonkly Limited, Regina House, 124 Finchley Road, London NW3 5JS.
CHANGES
We may make change to this Privacy Policy at any time by sending you an e-mail with the modified terms or by posting a copy of them on the Site. Any changes will take effect seven (7) days after the date of our e-mail or the date on which we post the modified terms on the Site, whichever is the earlier. Your continued use of the Site after that period expires means that you agree to be bound by the modified terms.
CONTACT US
This Site is owned by Zonkly Limited, a company incorporated in England. The registered office address of Zonkly Limited is Regina House, 124 Finchley Road, London NW3 5JS.
Our registered company number is 8233489
You can contact us via email on admin@stressbusting.co.uk or at the registered office address supplied above.
Take A Test
Therapy Selector
Take the Stress Test
Popular Posts
Read
Shared
1The most annoying telephone hold music of all time
213 tips on how to deal with exam stress
3Become a team player: dealing with workplace stress
4Cognitive Bias Modification
5Stress symptoms
Why every company should have an office dog17 kinds of stress-related illness2Caffeine and anxiety: 8 things to know36 ways to stop working too hard413 ways to take the stress out of commuting58 things to bear in mind about supplements for stress611 ways to deal with the boss from hell7Stress during pregnancy: is it dangerous?89 ways to cope with wedding stress9Stress-related hair loss10What is stress?116 tips on how to relieve stress12Symptoms of stress: what you need to know1312 ways to cope with too many emails145 reasons you need to start fantasizing1513 tips on how to deal with exam stress16Puppies help stressed students17Polls
Do you check emails before breakfast?
Yes
No
View Results
Loading ...
Autogenic (AT)
Ayurvedic Medicine
Biofeedback
Breathing
Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT)
Kinesiology (Applied)
Laughter therapy
Massage
Meditation
Mindfulness (MBSR)
Music Therapy
Neuro-linguistic programming (NLP)
